# Erhan Yaylali

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

+45 50 23 19 14

in linkedin.com/in/erhanyaylali

www.yaylali.net

erhanyaylali9@gmail.com

#### SUMMARY

I am a software developer with more than three and half years' experience in the field. As a person, I am great at collaborating, working as a team player and a very open-minded person. Besides developing websites, I have experience on working with UI/UX teams for design, handling SEO optimizations and communicating with customers. I am currently residing in Odense, Denmark.

#### SKILLS

JavaScript, jQuery . CSS and SASS

Detail Oriented

Problem solving (engineering)

React, Redux

Google Console and AWS - Good communication - Attention to detail

#### EDUCATION

# **Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering**

Istanbul Technical University • 2016 - 2021

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Hesehus A/S, Odense, Denmark

Frontend Developer • July 2022 - Present

- I am helping our customers to get better SEO results, have to them user friendly and accessible pages, high quality and sustainable software in technical development.
- By considering the budget and approach of customer and reality of project, I am helping them to determine roadmap for upcoming times, to analyze the current problems, to find good solutions for requirements for needs of both customers and the market.

#### Orion Innovation, Istanbul, Turkey

Full stack Developer • December 2021 - July 2022

- I implemented React Query system that improved the performance +30% than Redux system that was built.
- I integrated Google Cloud services for both frontend (React) and backend (Node JS) projects. I also implemented ORM for database in one of the layers, and Firebase DB for another.
- I integrated bidirectional communication between multiple layers by using Websocket.

# Yapı Kredi Technology, Istanbul, Turkey

Full stack Developer • July 2021 - December 2021

- I was building intra webpages by using React, Java, MySQL technologies for the lawyers. I was also focusing on user experience and accessibility of the the page.
- I was constant communication with other teams for data exchange and preparation of the future tasks.
- By implementing unit tests, I helped the project got 90% coverage.

## Ibtech, Gebze, Turkey

Jr Fullstack Developer • 02.2021 - 07.2021

 I created a new Micro react Project for a new requested feature. I also implemented Redux state system and Swagger to the project.